Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
- Film Writers and Directors, Publication (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: New talk start in TV-Film strike, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Loyalty oath row splits film guild, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Writers seek pay for TV film deals, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Directors Guild Acts to recall Mankiewicz, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Film Directors Guild aiming to add TV men, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Hollywood Digest - Screen writers guild seeks story, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Film writers end strike against TV, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 12: Writers film men reach compromise, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 13: Film guild moves against Fox cuts, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
  - Item 14: Screen writers defer pact vote, 1950-1952 (Box 328, Folder 3)
- Screen Actors Guild, Inc., Publication (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1933; Publication (Box 328, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: News Bulletin, 1961; Publication (Box 328, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1961 - no.1-7
  - Item 3: News Bulletin, 1963; Publication (Box 328, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1963
  - Item 4: Special Bulletin, 1960; Publication (Box 328, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1960 - no.1,-8,10-12
  - Item 5: Special Bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 328, Folder 4)
    Notes: 1962 - (Dec)
- National Federation of Salaried Unions, Publication (Box 328, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: White Collar Unionist, 1952; Publication (Box 328, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.8:no.1-6,8-11
  - Item 2: White Collar Unionist, 1953; Publication (Box 328, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.9:no.13,8,3-6,1
  - Item 3: White Collar Unionist, 1954; Publication (Box 328, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.10:no.7,1-2,4-5
  - Item 4: White Collar Unionist, 1955; Publication (Box 328, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.11:no.1-8
  - Item 5: White Collar Unionist, 1956; Publication (Box 328, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.12:no. 1-3
- American Fisherman and Cannery Workers, Publication (Box 329, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: American Fisherman and Cannery Worker, 1968; Publication (Box 329, Folder 1)
    Notes: v5:no.7,9
  - Item 2: American Fisherman and Cannery Worker, 1969; Publication (Box 329, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no.1-3,5
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU)., Publication (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Deep Sea Sailor's SIU Handbook, Publication (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Labor union history, 1970; Publication (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Surgical Schedule, Publication (Box 329, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Pension welfare and vacation benefits, 1970; Publication (Box 329, Folder 2)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America., Publication (Box 329, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Seafarers' Log, 1939; Publication (Box 329, Folder 3)
    Notes: v.1:no.18 (1939)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America., Publication (Box 329, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: The Seafarers' Log, 1939; Publication (Box 329, Folder 4)
    Notes: v.1:no.18 (1939). Second copy
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU)., Publication (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: U.S. Cargo preference laws: history of the laws, nature of the laws, administration of the laws, effect on U.S. tramp fleet, 1964; Publication (Box 330, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: The Merchant Marine Act of 1936: intent of the Act, administration of the Act, construction subsidies, operating subsidies, 1964; Publication (Box 330, Folder 1)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The SIU at war; true experiences in the war at sea of members of the Seafarers international union., 1944; Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: You Choose! -- SIU//NMU, Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: I had anchoritis, 1946-1947 (Box 330, Folder 2)
    Notes: Flyers/Booklets
  - Item 4: Two ways about it--, 1946-1947 (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Seafarers Organizing Program, 1947; Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
    Notes: Excerpt from the Nov.7,1947 issue of the Seafarers Log. Flyers/Booklets
  - Item 6: Official Shipping Rules (as amended July 31, 1946), Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Differences between SIU-NMU contracts and working conditions, 1948; Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Annual Report, 1943; Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: The Right to work fraud, Publication (Box 330, Folder 2)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU), Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The SIU at war; true experiences in the war at sea of members of the Seafarers international union., 1944; Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: The seafarers in World War II, 1951; Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
    Author: John Bunker
  - Item 3: All this happened: the story of American labor, Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: In the matter of proposed user tax on inland waterways: brief Inland Boatmen's Union of the Pacific, District Union of Seafarers' International Union of North America, AFL-CIO, 1956; Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: SIU wage scale - from 3/44 to 11/18/52, 1952; Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Seafarers welfare plan, Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Fortune, 1950; Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
    Notes: Dec-50
  - Item 8: Statement of Sailors' Union of Pacific in support of charges against recruitment.., Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: A local union election (Industrial Bulletin), 1953; Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
    Notes: August, 1953
  - Item 10: Labor-management reporting and disclosure act of 1959, Publication (Box 330, Folder 3)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU), Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Listen, Tankermen, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Strikes and strike strategy, 1948; Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: The inside story of the AMEU, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
    Author: Frank Fletcher
  - Item 4: Here's how brother!, 1945; Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Seafarers Organizing Program, 1947; Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: I had anchoritis, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Who talks for you?, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 8: Seamen! Here are the SIU conditions for you, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Money ain't everythinbut, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: It ain't hay!, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 11: Two ways about it - The AMEU way/The SIU way, 1953; Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
  - Item 12: The Bag: the story of a wasted life, Publication (Box 330, Folder 4)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Statement of the Seafarers International Union of Canada relative to the Report of the Industrial Inquiry Commission on the Disruption of Shipping, 1963; Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: All this happened: the story of American labor, Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Union-busting: Canadian style!, 1963; Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: This is the Harry Lundeberg School, Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: International, 1970; Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
    Notes: Fall 1970
  - Item 6: Paul Hall - Biography, Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Correspondence, 1961; Publication (Box 330, Folder 5)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Statement by Paul Hall, Pres. Seafarers, 1965; Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Statement by J. Andreae before President's maritime Advisory Committee, 1965; Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: H.R. 4256 - In the House of RepresentativesTo amend section 883 of the Internal Revene Code of 1954, 1965; Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Statement by Seafarers' on Oil Import quota program, 1965; Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Statement of Seafarers'to the Subcommittee on Federal Procurement and Regulation of the Joint Economic Committee, 1965; Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: NewsPress Release - Monday, March 29, 1965, Publication (Box 330, Folder 6)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU), Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Charges: what they constitute and how to handle them, Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: International Conference on Safety of Life at Sea, 1948; Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
    Notes: London-England-Apr. 23-Jun. 10-1948; report to the membership of the Seafarers International Union. Second copy
  - Item 3: Order!: how to conduct a union meeting on ship & shore, Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Seafarers organizers handbook, Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Shipboard handbook for crewmembers and delegates, Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: This is the SIU, Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Food for thought: 6 articles on timely union topics reprinted from Seafarers log, official organ of S.I.U., Atlantic & Gulf District, American Federation of Labor, 1949; Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Shipping guide for Seafarers: registration rules, shipping rules, transportation rule, Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: The Union News, 1968; Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.5:no. 7 (1968)
  - Item 10: The Union News, 1969; Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.6:no. 1-2 (1969)
  - Item 11: Specimen questions and answers for firemen examinations, 1948; Publication (Box 331, Folder 1)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America, Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Seafarers welfare plan, 1953; Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: For Seafarers and their families: The Seafarers Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Seafarers Log, 1956; Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
    Notes: 2nd section (Jan. 6, 1956)
  - Item 4: Seafarers Log, 1955; Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.17:no. 1
  - Item 5: Seafarers Log, 1954; Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.16:no. 1
  - Item 6: Your Dollar's Worth - reprinted from the Seafarers Log, 1955; Publication (Box 331, Folder 2)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU)., Publication (Box 331, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The Deep Sea Sailor's SIU Handbook, Publication (Box 331, Folder 3)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU)., Publication (Box 331, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Before the war shipping panel, National War Labor Board: in the matter of Pacific American Shipowners Association, and Marine Cooks & Stewards Association of the Pacific Coast: Appendix, Union exhibits, 1944; Publication (Box 331, Folder 4)
- National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Treacherous passage: the story of the maritime unions' twelve year fight against spies, goon squads, intrigue, murder and other shipowner devices of sabotage, 1942; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
    Author: Ruth Sutherland
  - Item 2: Story, National Union of Marine Cooks and Stewards, 1946; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: The delegate: a handbook for the MCS ships delegate, 1961; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: The strike as a weapon of labor, 1946; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Economic material on the maritime industry ..., 1946; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Twelve thousand marine cooks and stewards, 1944; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Facts for you about your SIU Health and Welfare Plan, Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Scale of wages and working rules, 1917; Publication (Box 331, Folder 5)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America. Pacific District, Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Joint release - Seamen's medical examination center opened today for San Francisco port (April 13), 1964; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Seafaring Men and Automation - some educational approaches, 1961; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Fact sheetSeamen's medical examination center, 1964; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Minutes of conventions, 1966; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Minutes of conventions, 1971; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Digest of direct payment plan, Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Statement in aid of candidacy of Harold A. (Spud) Robinson, 1960; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The SIU Pacific District Optical Benefit Program -- Eligibility requirements, limmitations and procedures for receiving benefits, 1964; Publication (Box 331, Folder 6)
- Seafarers' International Union of North America (SIU)., Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: SUP-PMA welfare fund: medical and hospital benefits for dependent wives and children, 1960; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: SIU Pacific District - PMA: Pension fund, Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: SIU Pacific District - PMA: Pension fund, 1962; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: Draft of the panel report, 1944; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: IUPW Views, 1962; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.16: no. 9 (1962)
  - Item 6: Statement o fSailors' Union of Pacific in support of charges against recruitment & manning division and training division of war shipping administration, 1944; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: Andrew Furuseth School of Seamanship "SS Invader", 1943; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: Annual Report, 1943; Publication (Box 331, Folder 7)
- International Seamen's Union of America, Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The seamen's view of the proposed codification of the navigation laws and the suggested amendments, 1927; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Andrew Furuseth, 1854-1938, Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: International safety treaty, 1929, why it should not be ratified; address over WNEW, Feb. 8th, 1936, Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
    Author: Silas Blake Axtel
  - Item 4: Rights of foreign and American seamen on foreign flag ships in American courts, 1955; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 5: Seamen's Journal, 1933; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.47: no. 4 (1933)
  - Item 6: Correspondence, 1934; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Read and Digest, Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 8: Attention please - 'Are the wobblies breaking strikes for nothing?...', 1922; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 9: Congressional Record - Proceedings and Debates of the 77th Congress, Second Session, 1942; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 10: Sunday, August 22, 1984, Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 11: Ninety-seventh birtheday Anniversary of Andrew Furuseth, 1951; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Expert on Admiralty Law enters tug-barge hearing, 1944; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Husky Axtell, NY Attorney goes to Sea, 1919; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
    Notes: article
  - Item 14: Longshoremen are now considered seamen by the latest decision of the Supreme Court, Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 15: International Convention for promoting safety of life at sea, 1929; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: Longshoremen's Brief, 1905; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: Safety at sea, 1936; Publication (Box 332, Folder 1)
    Notes: Delivered over Columbia Broadcasting System - February 26, 1936; 10:45 to 11:00 P.M.
- International Seamen's Union of America, Publication (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: The Seamen's Journal, 1920; Publication (Box 332, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.34:no. 9 (1920)
  - Item 2: The Seamen's Journal, 1922; Publication (Box 332, Folder 2)
    Notes: v.35:no. 27 (1922)
  - Item 3: Attention please - 'Are the wobblies breaking strikes for nothing?...', 1922; Publication (Box 332, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: The Seaman, 1923; Publication (Box 332, Folder 2)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 279 (1923)
- Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Service Employees International Union (SEIU)/1199 Healthcare Leadership Conference Packet, 1981; Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: OSHA - Report no. 14 (An Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Guidebook), 1975; Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Building Service Industry 1972-1976 -- Report no. 16, 1977; Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: union newspaper--"To all workers', Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Why not pick the best?' - newspaper for union workers, Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: The Concord - August 1969, Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Public Employees and Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 8: Apartment houses are doing a booming business, Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 9: Did you know that your boss pays union dues, Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 10: Service Employees International Union (SEIU) the union for hospital employees, Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
  - Item 11: Largest health care union Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Publication (Box 332, Folder 3)
- Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Unfair practices charged by '590', 1969; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: NUPO News, 1972-1973 (Box 332, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 1, no. 1,5 (1972-1973)
  - Item 3: NUPO News, 1973; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 2, no. 2-6 (1973)
  - Item 4: NUPO News, 1974; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 1-2 (1974)
  - Item 5: The Best way to get your car repaired(memo), 1969; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: 4% Wage increase?; Why is the Cornell University Employees' Union Local 590 different? (memos), 1969; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: The facts, 1969; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
    Notes: Memo. 2 copies
  - Item 8: Correspondence, 1971; Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Item 9: Dollars & Sense: The Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Consumer Newsletter - April, Sept., Dec. (1969), Oct (1970), 1969-1970 (Box 332, Folder 4)
  - Item 10: National Industry Pension Fund, Publication (Box 332, Folder 4)
- Service Employees International Union (SEIU), Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: What is a union?, 1981; Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
    Author: Althea; Chris Evans
  - Item 2: This manual is prepared as an aid for Local Officers and Stewards of (January 17, 1956), Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Dollas & Sense: The Service Employees International Union (SEIU) Consumer Newsletter - Summer (1968); April (1969); December (1969); Sept. (1969), 1968-1969 (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: A private letter for the use and information of Service Employees International Union (SEIU) leadership., 1972; Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Service Employees International Union, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Service Employees International Union (SEIU) plays no favorites, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: What it costs not to belong to a union, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Apartment houses are doing a booming business, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: Uncle Sam says yes you can, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 10: A helping hand, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 11: Do you need a union?, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 12: Scholarships for your children, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 13: Do you support higher education?, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
  - Item 14: Who says hospital workers need unions?, Publication (Box 332, Folder 5)
- Western States Service Station Employees' Union, Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1958; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 8, no. 6 (1958)
  - Item 2: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1959; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 1 (1959)
  - Item 3: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1959; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 13, no. 2-7 (1959)
  - Item 4: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1960; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 14, no. 1-11, 15 (1960)
  - Item 5: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1961; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 15, no. 2-8, 10-11 (1961)
  - Item 6: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1962-1963 (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 16, no. 1, 3-11 (1962-1963)
  - Item 7: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1964; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 17, no. 1 (1964)
  - Item 8: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1964; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 18, no. 2-6 (1964)
  - Item 9: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1965; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 19 no. 1-6 (1965)
  - Item 10: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1966; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 20, no. 2-5 (1966)
  - Item 11: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1967; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 21, no. 1-2, 4-6 (1967)
  - Item 12: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1962; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 10, 12 (1962)
  - Item 13: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1963; Publication (Box 332, Folder 6)
    Notes: no. 1-3 (1963)
- Western States Service Station Employees' Union, Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1968; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 22, no. 1-6 (1968)
  - Item 2: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1969; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 23, no. 1,3-6 (1969)
  - Item 3: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1970; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 24, no. 1-6 (1970)
  - Item 4: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1971; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 25, no. 1-6 (1971)
  - Item 5: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1972; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 26, no. 1-2, 4-6 (1972)
  - Item 6: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1973; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 27, no. 1, 3-6 (1973)
  - Item 7: The Western States Service Station Employees' Union News, 1974; Publication (Box 332, Folder 7)
    Notes: vol. 28, no. 1-3, 5 (1974)
- Sheet Metal Workers' International Association, Publication (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Rules and agreement of the Amalgamated Sheet Metal Workers International Alliance Local Union No. 28, New York and Vicinity and Employers Association of Roofers and Sheet Metal Workers of Greater New York and Adjacent Cities, Publication (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Sheet Metal Workers welfare plan: Local 58, Publication (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Item 3: William J. O'Brien, individually and as Secretary of Local No. 65 and Vice President of the Amalgamated Sheet Metal Workers, 1922; Publication (Box 332, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: Union Shop - This certifies, that the products of this shop are manufactured under fair conditions by competent union workmen, who are members of, Publication (Box 332, Folder 8)
    Notes: Poster
  - Item 5: The Shoe Reporter, Publication (Box 332, Folder 8)